(Howard:)No joke.
(Howard:)- She's sorry she's late.
- Oh, tell her it doesn't matter.
(Raj:)Tell her her eyes shimmer
Iike opalescent lilies...
(Raj:)...in the lake of the palace
of the celestial maidens.
(Howard:)Really?
That's the first thing you wanna say?
- I worked on it all night. Use it.
- I don't know the sign for "opalescent."
- Then spell it.
- I don't know how to spell it.
(Raj:)You're blowing this for me.
He likes your eyes, heh.
(Raj:)You're making me sound
Iike a caveman.
"Thank you, you have nice eyes too."
(Howard:)Really?
Ask her how many children she wants...
(Raj:)...and whatever number she says,
say, "Me too."
(Howard:)No.
(Raj:)Fine. Tell her I have a deep, sexy voice
Iike James Earl Jones.
(Howard:)She doesn't know
what James Earl Jones sounds like.